UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Photographs 6000/016 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- AFL-CIO Convention -- 11/2001 --- Mike Short, Bruce Raynor (Box 7, Folder 21)
  94 photos
- Officer's informal group (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Contact sheets (Box 8, Folder 2)
  4 contact sheets
- Jacob Potofsky (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Valentino Market Picketing (Box 8, Folder 4)
  87 photos, negatives
- Attaboy Novelty Company Strike (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Misc. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Local 169 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  5 photos, 28 slides
- Copper printing plate (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Company Store -- 4/2000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- LA Crowley - Fechhemeir -- 12/10-12/11/1998 and 12/4/1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  negatives, 28 photos
- Mystery? (Box 8, Folder 11)
- WestPoint Stevens, Inc. -- Drakes Branch, VA (Box 8, Folder 12)
  62 photos
- Unlabelled slides (Box 8, Folder 13)
  85 slides, negatives
- Laundry workers (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Hill visit (Box 8, Folder 15)
  10 slides
- UNITE- Questionable (Box 8, Folder 16)
  13 slides
- UNITE-Candids (Box 8, Folder 17)
  50 slides
- Southwest (Box 8, Folder 18)
  10 slides, negatives
- Officer's Formal Group (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Officers Solo (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Israel Histadrut Campaign (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Local 169-- 'Day in the life of Silverio Otero' -- 8/2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- UNITE Local 169, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  11 photos, negatives
- UNITE Party, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Adinah's Farms - Strike, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Proof sheets and negatives (Box 8, Folder 26)
  Proof sheets, negatives
- Local 169 - Immigrant Workers, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  77 photos, negatives, proof sheet
- Convention, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Convention, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Convention, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Convention, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- removed, photos consolidated in other boxes (Box 10)
- rolled photos too large for panoramic box (Box 11)
  Panoramic photos - - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Atlantic City, NJ, May 14-18, 1962, 23rd Biennial Convention; Testimonial Dinner-Dance in Honor of Thomas Flavell, The Waldorf-Astoria, November, 12, 1955 (2); Joint Meeting of the General Executive Board, Joint Board Managers and Local Representatives, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, February 5-7, 1947, Atlantic City, NJ; Twenty Ninth Convention, ILGWU Convention Hall, Atlantic City, May 10-18, 1956; Victory Celebration, Local 169, ACW of A, Manhattan Center, Jan. 31, 1962
- One photo moved to box 11, the rest to box 16 -- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Atlantic City, NJ, May 14-18, 1962, 23rd Biennial Convention (Box 12)
  1 panoramic photo in map folder
- UNITE - Portland, Me -- 10/2002 (Box 13)
  - UNITE-Portland, Me -- 10/2002 (Box 13)
    CD/DVD
- UNITE - Portland Me. - October 19, 2002 (Box 14)
  - UNITE-Portland, Me - October 19, 2002 (Box 14)
- UNITE/GAP press conference - 5/16/2002 (Box 15)
  - UNITE/GAP -- Press Conference -- 5/16/2002 (Box 15)
- Panoramic photos (11) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Proof of a portrait (un identified); Officers-Delegates of Local 169, New York City, May 13-24, 1940 (2); 8 Group shots (un identified)